Angela Thompson

Brentwood, TN 37027 Phone: 615-428-0189 | Email: amtgo25@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/angelathompson201/ |

GitHub: github.com/thomps0189 | Portfolio: https://thomps0189.github.io/react-portfolio/

Summary of Qualifications

Front-End Web Developer with a background in wealth management and a degree in psychology with fine attention to detail and enhancing user experience. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from Vanderbilt University; skills acquired in HTML/CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, MERN Stack, and more. Spent several years working in wealth management helping clients better use and understand the technology. Recently worked on a team of 4 to create a Fitness Tracker App and set up the conditional rendering and signup/login functionality. Excited to use new skills and transfer over existing skills to help create a great user experience and organized clean code.

Technical Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Moment.js, Node.js, jQuery UI, Express, AJAX, Git, Sequelize, MySQL, OOP, PWA's, NoSQL, IndexDB, MongoDB, MongoOse, React, MERN Stack

Projects

Fitness Tracker App | github.com/DuGBB/Lennons-Fitness-Super-App | ancient-fortress-4675.herokuapp.com

- · Collaborator on a team of 4 to create a website where a user can sign up/login and join classes or view/update their benchmarks for various fitness tests.
- · Created the functionality of the signup/login forms. Set up conditional rendering of the components in the navigation bar.
- · Tools/languages used: MERN Stack, Bootstrap, Apollo Server

National Park Vacation Planner | github.com/DuGBB/trail-lad | dugbb.github.io/trail-lad/

- · Collaborator on a team of 3 to create a website to allow users to find national parks near them in the selected state. The results pull up the name of the park, history, and nearby dining locations.
- · In charge of the design and HTML/CSS
- · Tools/languages used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, BootStrap

Bootcamp Real Estate Website | https://github.com/thomps0189/bootcamp-real-estate | https://calm-depths-28335.herokuapp.com/

- · Collaborator on a team of 4 to create a website to be used by a real estate manager and their tenants. Properties are listed and provide details such as bed/bath. Tenants are also able to submit maintenance requests to the landlord.
- · In charge of the login component, models, and seeds.
- · Tools/languages used: Sequelize, Bcrypt, Express, Handlebars, Node.js, MySQL

EXPERIENCE

Appalachian Trail

April 2021- August 2021

Long Distance Backpacker

• The Appalachian Trail is a 2,200 mile hiking-only trail from Springer Mountain, GA to Mt. Katahdin, ME. It is the longest hiking-only trail in the world and has existed since 1937. I successfully hiked over 1,000 miles through 7 states. I overcame many physical and mental obstacles and learned how to handle tough situations.

RBC Wealth Management, Boston, MA

July 2020- February 2021

Registered Client Associate

- · Client Associate on a team of 3 advisors. Fully responsible for account opening, paperwork, transactions, and account maintenance.
- · Created an annual review scheduling system for the existing and new clients
- · Helped team create spreadsheets for various organizational purposes and how to use Excel

Merrill Lynch, Brentwood, TN *Registered Client Associate*

January 2016- July 2020

- Fully responsible for the calendar of a Senior Vice President (Financial Advisor) including 170 client meetings per year. Contacted clients before meetings to collect data, prepared reports, sent meeting reminders, and confirmed all required items were discussed during and after the meeting, resulting in seamless and productive meetings.
- Customer Service first line of contact for 250 clients. Anticipated weekly or monthly needs and organized Salesforce so that all items were ready when the client needed it. Assisted clients with any monetary transactions, educated clients on how to use the company's technology and apps, and answered simple financial questions resulting in happy and loyal clients who felt confident coming to me for assistance before having to involve the Financial Advisor.
- Responsible for all administrative tasks creating daily reports, client profiles, ordering banking supplies, issuing checks, and opening accounts.
- Recognition:
 - o Winner of 2018 RSGA Top 1500 Client Associate's Award awarded to client associates who exceeded certain metrics by increasing client usage of technology
 - o One of 3 Client Associates in the Nashville Market to be invited to Phoenix, AZ for a conference with 150 other Client Associates from across the firm
- Series 7 and 66 Registered.

Spencer Stuart, Chicago, IL

June 2015- September 2015

Meeting Planning Group Intern for leading global executive search and consulting firm

- Organized and collected data for costs, potential meeting locations, and creative ideas for upcoming meetings
- Brainstormed and presented themes, activities, and event spaces for an upcoming international meeting
- Worked with meeting planners to learn about Cvent
- Created in-depth hotel site search reports and then presented to the meeting leader

EDUCATION:

Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN Full Stack Web Development

2021-2022

Course: Bootcamp Certificate

Miami University, Oxford, OH Bachelor of Arts

2015

Major: Psychology, Minor in Comparative Religion, studied abroad in Paris & London in 2014

Relevant Skills and Coursework:

- Senior Capstone- Consumer Psychology. Organized and presented a business plan to Textron Aviation to help increase retention rates and evolve employee culture
- Social Psychology, Developmental Psychology, Cognitive Psychology, Abnormal Psychology, Biopsychology, Statistics, Research Design and Analysis (advanced psychological statistics course)